JAPHETH DIEVOLE COBBINAH

Information Technology Expert | Web Developer | Computer Programmer | Cyber Security | Social Media Marketing | Database Management | Graphic Design

Mobile: +233 556 592 404 | Email: dievole7@gmail.com

CAREER SUMMARY

I am an Information Technology expert with more than 6 years of increasing Software and Website Development and Web App, Cybersecurity, database management and social media marketing experience. I am a self-motivated, highly organized individual capable of multitasking and seeking to utilize my knowledge, experience, skills and competence to help this institution to the best of my ability.

I am committed to professional and personal development, capable of communicating with all levels of organizational management and proficient in working under pressure with an optimistic attitude.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS/EXPERTISE

- Computer Programming
- Website Development
- WordPress
- Social Media promotion/marketing
- Search Engine Optimization
- Computer Hardware / Software
- SEO
- Cyber Security
- Computer Troubleshooting
- Database Management
- Content Curator
- Team Player
- Project Reporting
- Excellent writing skills

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Head, IT department - January 2020 - Present

Yehowa Asem Herbal Hospital

- Manage and update the company's website.
- Manage Hospital Management System
- Create and upload content unto the social media pages.
- Design various communication materials for publicity.
- Develop database management system to track and record patient's details.
- Manage and provide responses to enquiries from the public, the press, and related organizations.
- Lead and ensured quality video coverage and photography during event/field visit.
- Effectively manage all the social media platforms.
- Develop and implement social media plans and policies.
- Monitor all computers regularly to fix any emerging problem.
- Provide invoices and purchase any computer accessories required.

Cashier & IT Technician – February 2018- January 2020 Mansowa Herbal Centre

- Registered new patients at the hospital.
- Received all payments and accounted to the finance department.
- Searched for the folders and details of all old patients.
- Fixed all internet and computer challenges.

Information Technology Teacher (JHS Level) – March 2016 – February 2018 Dankwah Gyamerah Memorial School

- Developed course outline for each term.
- Prepared presentation and teaching note for each class session.
- Researched for books and available materials to aid student learning.
- Established positive atmosphere for learning during lecture session.
- Set examination questions at the end of each term.

IT & social media Officer – February 2014 – January 2016 NABA Life Foundation (NLF)

- Managed all the social media pages for the foundation.
- Prepared social media weekly content plan.
- Quarterly review the positive effect with the use of the social media for promotion.

• Responded to media enquiries or calls on behalf of the communications director.

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

Accra Technical University (ATU)
Degree in Computer Science
2022 – present

Aptech IT College Diploma in Information System Management 2018 – 2019

Our Lady of Mercy Senior High School WASSCE 2009 – 2013

PERSONAL QUALITIES

- Ability to work in a diverse environment
- Dedication and diligence in my work
- Very results- oriented
- Trustworthy
- Eager to learn
- Ability to meet deadlines
- Good human relation and communication skills
- Does not compromise on integrity
- Good Team Leader